{
    "subject": "resource/Upper_Shirley,_Virginia",
    "predicate": "property/longDirection",
    "object": "W",
    "human_readable": "The direction of Upper Shirley, Virginia is West.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9433112144470215,
            "question": "What direction is Upper Shirley, Virginia located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9224660396575928,
            "question": "If you were facing Upper Shirley, Virginia, which way would be West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169637560844421,
            "question": "Is Upper Shirley, Virginia located North or West?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8304300308227539,
            "question": "In what direction from its current location would you travel to reach Upper Shirley, Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8217609524726868,
            "question": "What is the opposite direction of Upper Shirley, Virginia's location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8053082823753357,
            "question": "Which cardinal direction describes the path towards Upper Shirley, Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7818906307220459,
            "question": "If you were traveling East from Upper Shirley, Virginia, which direction would you be heading in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6903461813926697,
            "question": "How would you describe the geographical orientation of Upper Shirley, Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5911572575569153,
            "question": "Which way do you need to travel from its current position to reach Upper Shirley, Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5237005949020386,
            "question": "What is the bearing of Upper Shirley, Virginia relative to True North?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The direction of Upper Shirley, Virginia is West.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8821_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which way do you need to travel from its current position to reach Upper Shirley, Virginia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8821_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the geographical orientation of Upper Shirley, Virginia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8821_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were traveling East from Upper Shirley, Virginia, which direction would you be heading in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8821_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8821_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions the GPS coordinates for Upper Shirley Vineyards as  N37\u00ba 20.7157 W77\u00ba 15.3993. This indicates its location is West of Richmond, Virginia but not simply \"West\". \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention the direction (North, South, East, or West) of Upper Shirley, Virginia. The documents provide information about its location and surroundings, but not its specific direction."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information about the geographical direction (whether it's west) of Upper Shirley Vineyards. The directions and locations provided in the documents refer to its proximity to Richmond, Virginia and the James River, but there is no mention of the specific cardinal direction."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the context provided suggesting or implying the direction of Upper Shirley, Virginia.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "GPS coordinates N37\u00ba 20.7157 W77\u00ba 15.3993 indicate a Westward location.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions that Upper Shirley Vineyards is located 20 miles outside of Richmond, Virginia, which implies that the direction would be away from Richmond and not towards the west.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provides the GPS coordinates for Upper Shirley Vineyards (N37\u00ba 20.7157 W77\u00ba 15.9393), which indicate that it is located in the western part of Virginia, not the west direction from an unspecified location.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}